{
  "admin": [
    {
      "name": "admin",
      "password": "1234"
    }
  ],
  "subject": [
    {
      "name": "Maths",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "Maths2",
      "id": 2
    }
  ],
  "exam": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Maths",
      "desc": "This is Math Exam",
      "date": "17-9-2021 17:49:39",
      "marks": "5",
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "passMarks": "3",
      "level": "Easy"
    },
    {
      "name": "Maths",
      "desc": "this is maths2 exam",
      "level": "easy",
      "passMarks": "4",
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "marks": "5",
      "date": "15-11-2023 10:52:39",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Maths2",
      "desc": "this is maths3",
      "level": "easy",
      "passMarks": "3",
      "totalQuestion": "4",
      "marks": "4",
      "date": "15-11-2023 12:24:29",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "Question": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "qname": "10-5 ?",
      "optionOne": "3",
      "optionTwo": "1",
      "optionThree": "2",
      "optionFour": "5",
      "answer": "5",
      "ename": {
        "id": "1"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "qname": "10+5 ?",
      "optionOne": "3",
      "optionTwo": "1",
      "optionThree": "4",
      "optionFour": "15",
      "answer": "15",
      "ename": {
        "id": "1"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      }
    },
    {
      "qname": "10*5",
      "optionOne": "10",
      "optionTwo": "5",
      "optionThree": "50",
      "optionFour": "2",
      "answer": "50",
      "ename": {
        "id": "1"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "qname": "110-10 ?",
      "optionOne": "110",
      "optionTwo": "100",
      "optionThree": "10",
      "optionFour": "1",
      "answer": "100",
      "ename": {
        "id": "1"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "qname": "2+3=?",
      "optionOne": "1",
      "optionTwo": "5",
      "optionThree": "4",
      "optionFour": "3",
      "answer": "5",
      "ename": {
        "id": "2"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths2"
      },
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "qname": "5+1=?",
      "optionOne": "6",
      "optionTwo": "4",
      "optionThree": "3",
      "optionFour": "2",
      "answer": "6",
      "ename": {
        "id": "2"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths2"
      },
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "qname": "5+5=?",
      "optionOne": "10",
      "optionTwo": "4",
      "optionThree": "51",
      "optionFour": "1",
      "answer": "10",
      "ename": {
        "id": "1"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "qname": "3+4=?",
      "optionOne": "2",
      "optionTwo": "7",
      "optionThree": "5",
      "optionFour": "8",
      "answer": "7",
      "ename": {
        "id": "2"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths2"
      },
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "qname": "3+3=?",
      "optionOne": "2",
      "optionTwo": "7",
      "optionThree": "6",
      "optionFour": "8",
      "answer": "6",
      "ename": {
        "id": "2"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths2"
      },
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "qname": "3+5=?",
      "optionOne": "2",
      "optionTwo": "7",
      "optionThree": "6",
      "optionFour": "8",
      "answer": "8",
      "ename": {
        "id": "2"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths2"
      },
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "qname": "1+3=?",
      "optionOne": "3",
      "optionTwo": "2",
      "optionThree": "4",
      "optionFour": "7",
      "answer": "4",
      "ename": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths3"
      },
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "qname": "5+7=?",
      "optionOne": "14",
      "optionTwo": "15",
      "optionThree": "12",
      "optionFour": "76",
      "answer": "12",
      "ename": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths3"
      },
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "qname": "1+9=?",
      "optionOne": "6",
      "optionTwo": "10",
      "optionThree": "34",
      "optionFour": "13",
      "answer": "10",
      "ename": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths3"
      },
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "qname": "2+7=?",
      "optionOne": "6",
      "optionTwo": "9",
      "optionThree": "13",
      "optionFour": "16",
      "answer": "9",
      "ename": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "sname": {
        "name": "maths3"
      },
      "id": 13
    }
  ],
  "Result": [
    {
      "status": "Pass",
      "score": 3,
      "email": {
        "email": "ram@gmail.com"
      },
      "edate": "15-11-2023 17:14:0",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "5",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "status": "Fail",
      "score": 2,
      "email": {
        "email": "teststud@gmail.com"
      },
      "edate": "15-11-2023 17:18:55",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "5",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "status": "Fail",
      "score": 2,
      "email": {
        "email": "teststud@gmail.com"
      },
      "edate": "15-11-2023 17:20:3",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "5",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "status": "Pass",
      "score": 3,
      "email": {
        "email": "test@gmailcom"
      },
      "edate": "16-11-2023 17:20:37",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "5",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "status": "Fail",
      "score": 0,
      "email": {
        "email": "test@gmailcom"
      },
      "edate": "16-11-2023 17:28:38",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "5",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "status": "Fail",
      "score": 2,
      "email": {
        "email": "test@gmailcom"
      },
      "edate": "16-11-2023 17:29:5",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "5",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "status": "Fail",
      "score": 1,
      "email": {
        "email": "test@gmailcom"
      },
      "edate": "16-11-2023 17:42:19",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "4",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "status": "Pass",
      "score": 4,
      "email": {
        "email": "test@gmailcom"
      },
      "edate": "16-11-2023 17:54:20",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "4",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "4",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "status": "Pass",
      "score": 4,
      "email": {
        "email": "test@gmailcom"
      },
      "edate": "16-11-2023 17:54:49",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "5",
      "examId": {
        "id": "2"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "5",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "status": "Pass",
      "score": 4,
      "email": {
        "email": "test@gmail.com"
      },
      "edate": "16-11-2023 17:55:52",
      "sname": {
        "name": "Maths"
      },
      "totalMarks": "4",
      "examId": {
        "id": "3"
      },
      "totalQuestion": "4",
      "id": 10
    }
  ],
  "user": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "ram",
      "email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "password": "1234"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "shiv",
      "email": "shiv@gmail.com",
      "password": "1234"
    },
    {
      "name": "Vishnu",
      "email": "vishnu@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "Agni",
      "email": "agni@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "teststud",
      "email": "teststud@gmail.com",
      "password": "12345",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "name": "test",
      "email": "test@gmail.com",
      "dob": "2015-01-14",
      "password": "1234",
      "id": 6
    }
  ]
}